[
    {
        "question": "In which continent would you find the Niger river?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the Earth`s largest continent?",
        "answer": "Asia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Sao Tome and Principe?",
        "answer": "Sao Tome"
    },
    {
        "question": "What continent is Sao Tome and Principe located in?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country would you find the motor racing circuit called Kyalami?",
        "answer": "South Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the world`s only alpine parrot?",
        "answer": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where will you find `The Great White Way`?",
        "answer": "Broadway, New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Delaware?",
        "answer": "Dover"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country`s capital is Belmopan?",
        "answer": "Belize"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Belize`s capital?",
        "answer": "Belmopan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Portugal?",
        "answer": "Lisbon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Tunisia?",
        "answer": "Tunis"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which African country would you find the towns of Kumasi and Cape?",
        "answer": "Ghana"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what non-Spanish-speaking city would you find the Spanish Steps?",
        "answer": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "Belgium`s name is derived from what Roman province?",
        "answer": "Gallia Belgica"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which four countries share borders with Belgium?",
        "answer": "France, Germany, Netherlands and Luxembourg"
    },
    {
        "question": "The popular tourist destination, Amalfi, is located in which Italian region?",
        "answer": "Campania"
    },
    {
        "question": "The popular tourist destination, Amalfi, is located in which province in the Italian Campania region?",
        "answer": "Salerno"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the literal translation of Montenegro`s name?",
        "answer": "Black mountain"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Montenegro?",
        "answer": "Podgorica"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Mount Snowdon`s Welsh name `Yr Wyddfe` roughly translate to?",
        "answer": "The tumulus, or the barrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Mount Snowdon roughly translate to from Old English?",
        "answer": "Snow hill"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Maldives?",
        "answer": "Mal\u00e9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mal\u00e9 is the capital of which Asian country?",
        "answer": "Maldives"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mal\u00e9 is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Maldives"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city can you find the famed Arch of Hadrian?",
        "answer": "Athens, Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "Twenty-two months of negotiation and the 1998 Good Friday Agreement ended violence in what nation?",
        "answer": "Northern Ireland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first governor of Hong Kong?",
        "answer": "Sir Henry Arthur Blake"
    },
    {
        "question": "What currency does the former Soviet republic of Belarus use?",
        "answer": "Rubles"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the Czech foreign minister who died mysteriously following the Communist coup in that country in 1948?",
        "answer": "Jan Masaryk"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who preceded Fidel Castro as political leader of Cuba?",
        "answer": "Fulgencio Batista"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who took over as the top civilian administrator of Iraq in May 2003",
        "answer": "Paul Bremer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lusaka is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Zambia"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country is the historic city of Bam?",
        "answer": "Iran"
    },
    {
        "question": "The World`s first `sister cities` were what Spanish city and its US midwestern namesake?",
        "answer": "Toledo"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state`s National Guard still calls itself `the Green Mountain Boys`?",
        "answer": "Vermont"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find the Golden Gate Park?",
        "answer": "San Francisco"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find Battery Park?",
        "answer": "New York City"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find Hyde Park?",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest body of fresh water in the world by surface area?",
        "answer": "Lake Superior"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest body of fresh water by volume?",
        "answer": "Lake Baikal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country owns Easter Island?",
        "answer": "Chile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Easter Island is part of which country?",
        "answer": "Chile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Easter Island is part of which South American country?",
        "answer": "Chile"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city would you find Red Square?",
        "answer": "Moscow"
    },
    {
        "question": "What`s the largest freshwater lake in the world by surface area?",
        "answer": "Lake Superior"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city was the 2000 movie `Gladiator` filmed?",
        "answer": "Ouarzazate"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest national park in Canada?",
        "answer": "Georgian Bay Islands National Park, Ontario"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which body of water is the Nile River`s primary reservoir?",
        "answer": "Lake Victoria"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest elevation capital city in Asia?",
        "answer": "Thimphu, Bhutan"
    }
]